<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Apps on GaweTech</title><link>https://gawetech.com/category/apps/</link><description>Recent content in Apps on GaweTech</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;#169; &lt;strong>GaweTech&lt;/strong> Made with ❤️ using Hugo 0.95.0</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 13:29:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gawetech.com/category/apps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There are Two OneNotes in the Microsoft Store, which one to choose?</title><link>https://gawetech.com/two-onenotes-microsoft-store/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 13:29:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/two-onenotes-microsoft-store/</guid><description>Microsoft has recently released OneNote for Windows quietly. This means that currently there are two versions of OneNote, namely OneNote for Windows 10 (which we usually use) and OneNote for Windows (which was just released in the Microsoft Store).</description></item><item><title>Beware, Installing Mod APKs for Smartphones Can Be Dangerous</title><link>https://gawetech.com/install-apk-mod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 22:50:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/install-apk-mod/</guid><description>Mod APKs can be found in games or applications that we can download on unofficial platforms. Mod APKs in games can make users feel premium features for free, such as all game progress, lots of in-game money, high levels, etc.</description></item><item><title>Remove Annoying Adware (Malware Ads) for All Devices</title><link>https://gawetech.com/remove-adware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 12:40:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/remove-adware/</guid><description>The most common adware around us is Adware that infects browsers like chrome, firefox, etc. which are able to install and replace the default search engine.</description></item><item><title>Do I Need to Install Antivirus on Windows 11?</title><link>https://gawetech.com/windows-11-need-antivirus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 22:22:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/windows-11-need-antivirus/</guid><description>You don&amp;rsquo;t need to rush to install an antivirus on Windows 11 because your system already has it.
Windows 11 comes with many improvements in several sectors such as performance, user experience, design, and security.</description></item><item><title>8 New Differences Microsoft Defender vs. Windows Defender</title><link>https://gawetech.com/microsoft-windows-defender-difference/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 21:00:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/microsoft-windows-defender-difference/</guid><description>Microsoft has officially launched the Microsoft Defender application for several platforms ranging from Windows, Android, iOS, and macOS.
Previously, Microsoft already had Windows Defender which was built into the Windows operating system.</description></item><item><title>Telegram Premium, What are the Features and Cost?</title><link>https://gawetech.com/telegram-premium-features-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 13:00:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/telegram-premium-features-cost/</guid><description>Telegram premium or paid service officially launched at the end of June. Its increasingly clear presence is marked by the appearance of a beta version on the App Store with version 8.</description></item></channel></rss>