<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on GaweTech</title><link>https://gawetech.com/articles/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on GaweTech</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;#169; &lt;strong>GaweTech&lt;/strong> Made with ❤️ using Hugo 0.95.0</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 23:31:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gawetech.com/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dynamic Island Coming to All iPhone 15 Models</title><link>https://gawetech.com/dynamic-island-all-iphone-models/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 23:31:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/dynamic-island-all-iphone-models/</guid><description>The Dynamic Island feature is starting to be embedded on the iPhone 14 Pro &amp;amp; iPhone 14 Pro Max as a replacement for the notch on the previous model.</description></item><item><title>7 Mods to Improve Mechanical Keyboard, Easy and Cheap</title><link>https://gawetech.com/mechanical-keyboard-mods/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 21:39:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/mechanical-keyboard-mods/</guid><description>The existence of a mechanical keyboard can be addictive because it has a variety of ease to customize. Not just keycaps and switches, but mechanical keyboards have more potential than that.</description></item><item><title>Top 10 Recommended Mechanical Keyboards Under $100</title><link>https://gawetech.com/mechanical-keyboard-under-100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 21:35:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/mechanical-keyboard-under-100/</guid><description>Mechanical keyboards are indeed sold more expensive than regular keyboards (keyboards that use membranes). However, this is in accordance with the features and technology embedded in the mechanical keyboard.</description></item><item><title>73 PC / Console Games on Android &amp; iOS Without Emulator</title><link>https://gawetech.com/pc-console-games-android-ios/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 22:22:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/pc-console-games-android-ios/</guid><description>A total of 73 lists of games on your PC or console that were ported or converted to Android &amp;amp; iOS you can now play without having to use an emulator.</description></item><item><title>Beware, Installing Mod APKs for Smartphones Can Be Dangerous</title><link>https://gawetech.com/install-apk-mod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 22:50:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/install-apk-mod/</guid><description>Mod APKs can be found in games or applications that we can download on unofficial platforms. Mod APKs in games can make users feel premium features for free, such as all game progress, lots of in-game money, high levels, etc.</description></item><item><title>Remove Annoying Adware (Malware Ads) for All Devices</title><link>https://gawetech.com/remove-adware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 12:40:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/remove-adware/</guid><description>The most common adware around us is Adware that infects browsers like chrome, firefox, etc. which are able to install and replace the default search engine.</description></item><item><title>Shutdown, Sleep or Hibernate. Which is Best for Laptops?</title><link>https://gawetech.com/shutdown-sleep-hibernate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 23:10:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/shutdown-sleep-hibernate/</guid><description>To turn off a laptop, there are generally shutdown, sleep, or hibernate options. The three modes have almost the same function in turning off the laptop.</description></item><item><title>Do I Need to Install Antivirus on Windows 11?</title><link>https://gawetech.com/windows-11-need-antivirus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 22:22:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/windows-11-need-antivirus/</guid><description>You don&amp;rsquo;t need to rush to install an antivirus on Windows 11 because your system already has it.
Windows 11 comes with many improvements in several sectors such as performance, user experience, design, and security.</description></item><item><title>8 New Differences Microsoft Defender vs. Windows Defender</title><link>https://gawetech.com/microsoft-windows-defender-difference/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 21:00:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/microsoft-windows-defender-difference/</guid><description>Microsoft has officially launched the Microsoft Defender application for several platforms ranging from Windows, Android, iOS, and macOS.
Previously, Microsoft already had Windows Defender which was built into the Windows operating system.</description></item><item><title>Review of 10 Best Laptop Brand Recommendations &amp; Prices (2022)</title><link>https://gawetech.com/best-laptop-brand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 15:03:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/best-laptop-brand/</guid><description>Even though laptops are now almost a primary need, not a few people are still having trouble choosing the best laptop brand for them.</description></item><item><title>Telegram Premium, What are the Features and Cost?</title><link>https://gawetech.com/telegram-premium-features-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 13:00:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/telegram-premium-features-cost/</guid><description>Telegram premium or paid service officially launched at the end of June. Its increasingly clear presence is marked by the appearance of a beta version on the App Store with version 8.</description></item><item><title>8 Best Features in macOS Ventura, iPhone Can Be a Webcam</title><link>https://gawetech.com/macos-ventura-features/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 22:11:04 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://gawetech.com/macos-ventura-features/</guid><description>macOS Ventura, the latest operating system from Apple comes in an update for Mac or Macbook devices.
Apple officially announced the latest operating system together at the Worldwide Developers Conference or WWDC 2022 on Monday (6/6/2022) United States time.</description></item></channel></rss>